(Bernadette:)That's how I take it.
(Howard:)This is perfect.
(Howard:)I hope this moment
never ends.
(Bernadette:)Me, too.
(Howard:)Well, gotta go.
Oh!
(Bernadette:)Already?
Why don't you stay over?
(Howard:)I'd love to, but you know
(Howard:)my mother needs me in
the morning.
(Bernadette:)Please, I think the woman can
manage to put a wig on by herself.
(Howard:)It's not just the wig.
(Howard:)It's pinning her hair up,
drawing on her eyebrows.
(Howard:)It's a two-person job.
(Bernadette:)It's just, when you leave right
after we make love,
(Bernadette:)it makes me feel...
(Bernadette:)cheap.
(Howard:)Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
(Howard:)What can I do?
(Bernadette:)Stay.
(Howard:)Okay.
(Howard:)Like, what, another five,
ten minutes?
(Bernadette:)Go home.